{
  "type": "LOINC",
  "code": "defaultAnswerForm",
  "name": "Fields with default answers",
  "items": [
    {
      "question": "Boolean field with default",
      "questionCode": "blField",
      "dataType": "BL",
      "defaultAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Integer field with default",
      "questionCode": "intField",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "INT",
      "defaultAnswer": 24,
      "displayControl": {},
      "questionCodeSystem": "LOINC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Decimal field",
      "questionCode": "decField",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "REAL",
      "defaultAnswer": 3.14159,
      "displayControl": {},
      "questionCodeSystem": "LOINC"
    },
    {
      "question": "String field",
      "questionCode": "strField",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "*"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "ST",
      "defaultAnswer": "Green",
      "displayControl": {},
      "questionCodeSystem": "LOINC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Date field",
      "questionCode": "dateField",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "DT",
      "defaultAnswer": "t",
      "displayControl": {},
      "questionCodeSystem": "LOINC"
    },
    {
      "question": "List via answer label",
      "questionCode": "ansLabelDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CWE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R", "label": "i" },
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B", "label": "ii" },
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G", "label": "iii" }
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"label": "ii"}
    },
    {
      "question": "List via answer code",
      "questionCode": "ansCodeDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R", "label": "i" },
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B", "label": "ii" },
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G", "label": "iii" }
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"}
    },
    {
      "question": "List via answer code, unlabeled",
      "questionCode": "ansCodeDefaultNoLabel",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R"},
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B"},
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G"}
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"}
    },
    {
      "question": "Radio buttons via answer code",
      "questionCode": "radioAnsCodeDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R", "label": "i" },
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B", "label": "ii" },
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G", "label": "iii" }
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"},
      "displayControl": {
        "answerLayout": {
          "type": "RADIO_CHECKBOX",
          "columns": 2
        }
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Check boxes via answer code",
      "questionCode": "checkBoxAnsCodeDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "*"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R", "label": "i" },
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B", "label": "ii" },
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G", "label": "iii" }
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"},
      "displayControl": {
        "answerLayout": {
          "type": "RADIO_CHECKBOX",
          "columns": 2
        }
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Radio buttons via answer code, unlabeled",
      "questionCode": "radioAnsCodeDefaultNoLabel",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R"},
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B"},
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G"}
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"},
      "displayControl": {
        "answerLayout": {
          "type": "RADIO_CHECKBOX",
          "columns": 2
        }
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Multi-select list via answer code",
      "questionCode": "multiSelAnsCodeDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "*"
      },
      "dataType": "CNE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R", "label": "i" },
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B", "label": "ii" },
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G", "label": "iii" }
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": {"code": "B"}
    },
    {
      "question": "CWE not-on-list value",
      "questionCode": "ansTextDefault",
      "questionCardinality": {
        "min": "1",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "header": false,
      "editable": "1",
      "answerCardinality": {
        "min": "0",
        "max": "1"
      },
      "dataType": "CWE",
      "answers": [
        {"text": "Red", "code": "R"},
        {"text": "Blue", "code": "B"},
        {"text": "Green", "code": "G"}
      ],
      "defaultAnswer": "Blue"
    }
  ],
  "templateOptions": {
    "formHeaderItems": [{
      "question": "Date Done",
      "questionCode": "date_done",
      "dataType": "DT",
      "answers": "",
      "answerCardinality": {"min": "1", "max": "1"},
      "displayControl": {"colCSS": [{"name": "width", "value": "10em"}, {"name": "min-width", "value": "4em"}]},
      "defaultAnswer": "t"
    }, {
      "question": "Time Done",
      "questionCode": "time_done",
      "dataType": "TM",
      "answers": "",
      "displayControl": {"colCSS": [{"name": "width", "value": "12em"}, {"name": "min-width", "value": "4em"}]}
    }, {
      "question": "Where Done",
      "questionCode": "where_done",
      "dataType": "CWE",
      "answers": [{"text": "Home", "code": "1"}, {"text": "Hospital", "code": "2"}, {
        "text": "MD Office",
        "code": "3"
      }, {"text": "Lab", "code": "4"}, {"text": "Other", "code": "5"}],
      "displayControl": {"colCSS": [{"name": "width", "value": "30%"}, {"name": "min-width", "value": "4em"}]}
    }, {
      "question": "Comment",
      "questionCode": "comment",
      "dataType": "ST",
      "answers": "",
      "displayControl": {"colCSS": [{"name": "width", "value": "70%"}, {"name": "min-width", "value": "4em"}]}
    }]
  }
}
